A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grant and Program Reviews, SG 2, Series 9 FA1134
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Grant and Program Reviews, SG 2, Series 9
1984-1993
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1134
2.75 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box
Arrangement
As received.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Records in this series were transferred to RAC in October 1996.
Scope and Contents
A selection of grant, project and program review sessions from the mid-1980s through the mid-1990s.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
- Grant Review Sessions - Commonwealth Fund, 1987 August (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
- Grant Review Sessions - Commonwealth Fund, 1987 October (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Grant Review Sessions - Living at Home Program, 1987 December (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
- Grant Review Sessions - Living at Home Program, 1988 November (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Grant Review Sessions - Living at Home Program, 1988 October (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Program Review Sessions - Task Force on Academic Health Centers, 1988 February (Box 3, Folder 12-15)
- Program Review Sessions - Youth Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 16, Box 4, Folder 17)
- Program Review Sessions - Nursing, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
- Grant Review Session - Children's Defense Fund, 1989 June (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Program Review Sessions - Saving Lives Program, 1989, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21-23, Box 5, Folder 24)
- Program Development Seminar, 1989 August (Box 5, Folder 25-26)
- Management Seminar, 1987 August-1988 June (Box 5, Folder 27)
- The Commonwealth Fund at Hurricane Island Outward Bound School, 1987 August; 12 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11749)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  Scope and Contents
  Management seminar.
  Related Materials
  From Box: 5 [A0000000075600], Folder: 27
- Grant Review Sessions - Commonwealth Fund, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28-29, Box 6, Folder 30)
- Program Review Sessions - Grants Monitoring Program, 1993 January (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Program Review Sessions - Consumer Choice in Home Care, 1990 January (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Program Review Sessions - Picker-Commonwealth Fund Patient-Centered Care Program, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Program Review Sessions - Career Beginnings Evaluation Meeting, 1990 May (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Project Review - Angioplasty, 1990 September (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Program Review Sessions - Americans Over-50 at Work Program (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Program Review Sessions - Health Care and Nursing, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Program Review Sessions - Sponsor-A-Scholar Program (Box 6, Folder 38)